24 Sep 2012

Issues:

-- Paste not working
-- Undo copies sections of the screen when trying to reverse a selection move
-- Zoom does not do anything on click. Will only do it on ToolStrip button clicks
-- Zoom % Combo is allowing text to be entered. Lock down until can support flexible zooming


Questions:
-- Need the Clipboard channel still?

Completed Tasks:
-- Converted the Channel object from list of UINT to list of POINT structs, supports going off the canvas, into negative numbers


Yet To Do:
Profile Channel Import
Image Stamping
	-- Use something like the move channel
	-- Need bitmaps
	-- Need to get custom stamp working/tested
Test with Vixen
Free-standing EXE
Use original form for Original UI, have new form as a popover, hide the orignal form.	
Icicle Cursor
KeyBindings 
KeyChords
Text Tool
	Use an Input box to get the text string, paint over onto the PaintPane
	Locate some "bitmap" fonts
Fill Tool	
Add a line in the Channel explorer to represent the background image
Icon for Channel on CE
Channel Explorder - context menu items: 
	Hide other Channels
	Show all Channels
	Hide Background image (on bg image)
	Show Background image (on bg image)
	Set Brightness (on bg image)